question_data = [
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Type 1 diabetes is a result of the liver working improperly.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Anatomy considers the forms of macroscopic structures such as organs and organ systems.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Scientists accidentally killed the once known world's oldest living creature, a mollusc, known to be aged as 507 years old.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Centripedal force is an apparent force that acts outward on a body moving around a center, arising from the body's inertia.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium's symbol is the letter K.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
